- When we go up later...
- Mr. Wu,
- Please take care of him.
- Drink some more.
I can't drink anymore.
I'm going back for a moment.
- What's wrong?
- I left my phone in the room.
Go with the director first.
I'll be there in a bit.
We'll be waiting for you.
Zhen Xin.
Motherfucker!
Fuck.
Wu Rong.
Zhun.
You're awake?
Yes.
I'm awake.
What?
Then what are you two...
We're rehearsing a scene.
Rehearsing?
Right here?
At this hour?
It's true. We really are rehearsing.
Zhun, you're drunk.
Come with me.
He was actually awake.
Fuck.
[Episode 4]
Wu Rong. Just now...
Well...
I think I left my key card in the private room.
I'll go back and get it.
Wait for me here.
Wu Rong.
Don't hurt him.
Don't worry. I won't.
Want to fight?
Come on.
I'm right here.
Listen.
You'd better not have
any indecent thoughts about Zhun.
Or what?
My fists will cripple you.
I don't give a damn
if you're the Best Actor or not.
Fuck.
I didn't find it.
Maybe... I left it in the room.
Look at my memory.
Wu Rong.
I really was looking for the room key.
We haven't had a chance
to chat like this in a long time.
How about we share the room tonight?
Okay.
Silly boy.
Where are you going?
The bed is too small for two.
I'll sleep on the sofa.
Oh.
Is it because my snoring bothers you?
My wife always complains, too.
I'll sleep on the sofa.
You just got injured today.
You need enough sleep to recover quickly.
No, Wu Rong.
I just feel a bit awkward.
Back when we were training,
a dozen of us were all crammed
onto one big bunk.
Didn't we all get through it?
Now you find it awkward?
Maybe I've gotten used to being alone.
Are you used to sleeping alone,
or just not used to sleeping with me?
No, Wu Rong.
Don't overthink it.
I'll sleep on the sofa.
Forget it. You're weak as a kitten.
Besides, I'm used to sleeping on the sofa.
My wife's temper...
She's much harder to please than Dan Yi.
Dan Yi has a good temper.
Women...
You only see their true temper after marriage.
You two are getting married soon, right?
Zhun.
I read the script.
Gao Zhun's character background...
A single-parent family.
A very strict mother.
Why does it sound so familiar?
Yeah.
Zhun.
I feel like you've changed a bit.
Over these years...
Have you been having a hard time?
Wu Rong, I'm fine.
"I'm fine." You say that when you're hurt.
You say that when you have no work.
Even when your mother passed away,
you said you were fine.
Zhun, do you even see me as your friend?
Every time I ask you,
you're always like this.
It's not a disgrace to admit you're in pain.
Wu Rong, don't overthink it.
I... I'm really fine.
If you don't want to talk about it,
I won't ask anymore.
Anyway, this movie is a great opportunity.
Not only are you acting opposite Zhen Xin,
but you're also the lead.
Seize the chance and aim for an award.
Then your career's winter will be over.
Don't worry, Wu Rong.
I'll work hard.
Yeah.
You have to.
Zhun.
Remember what I said.
Acting is acting.
Life is life.
Besides, Dan Yi is still waiting for you.
[Feng Yun Ting]
Honey.
Why aren't you asleep? Miss me again?
Are you coming to visit the set or not?
What's the rush?
Wait until I finish this campaign, okay?
I have to wait for my schedule to clear up.
I have a pretty long vacation coming up.
When that time comes,
I'll come stay with you, how's that?
I'll stay for a few extra days.
I've never been to Coconut City before.
Honey.
Why aren't you saying anything?
You're not mad, are you?
What are you doing, Honey?
Shut up.
Stop it.
Director Chen, thank you
for your understanding and care.
Ms. Qin, are you done with your other scenes?
Yes, I am.
You have no idea.
They originally wanted me for two more days.
But I told them Director Chen
only gave me a day's worth of time,
and that he was already being very generous.
Right? So, I rushed back overnight.
Don't worry, Director Chen.
I won't delay the progress here.
Good.
Get me a cup of coffee later.
Sure.
Just perform as usual in today's scene.
No problem, Director Chen.
I have full confidence in your acting.
It's all thanks to your guidance.
Go to the dressing room and wait for me.
You...
Were you okay yesterday?
I'm fine.
Where's Wu Rong?
He doesn't have any scenes this morning.
He was still sleeping when I left.
You two slept together?
Wu Rong and I...
haven't seen each other in a long time.
We were just catching up.
He slept on the sofa.
Wu Rong didn't mean any harm.
He just cares too much.
He was just a bit impulsive.
Zhang Zhun, come here for a second.
Okay.
I'll head over there then.
I care, too.
What?
Nothing.
I said, focus on your acting.
Charles.
I'm so happy to see you.
I didn't expect you to come.
Think of it as a bonus service.
Dr. Fang.
That's a nice tie.
Thank you.
I really like this one.
All right.
We're here to see the exhibition together.
Let's just relax.
I don't want to hear your awkward flattery.
Let's go.
Come on.
These sculptures...
are very unique.
It's a specific style.
Modernism.
From an artist's perspective,
do you think the male body is more beautiful,
or the female body?
I drew people every day in art school.
I got sick of it.
In my eyes, men and women
are no different at all.
It seems...
you pursue pure aesthetics.
Not just aesthetics.
But also...
love.
Dr. Fang.
What are you...
How is your relationship with Lin Lin lately?
You...
Did you notice
that we're about to break up?
Why?
I...
I can't satisfy her.
In what way?
So, this is where you two snuck off to.
How ungentlemanly.
I only went to the bathroom,
and you didn't even wait for me.
Sorry.
I was just so captivated.
I didn't even realize.
Excuse me.
I need to take this call.
You guys go ahead. I'll find you in a bit.
Hello, Justin.
Give me a second.
Let him talk. Let's go.
Zuo Lin Lin.
I don't want him to get the wrong idea.
Justin.
I don't like this arrangement.
Can't you just follow my work schedule?
Do you remember that exhibition in New York?
It was a lot like today.
Who is Mr. Gao calling?
Justin.
One of his subordinates.
To be honest,
I'm sick of hearing that name.
Subordinate?
Why do you care so much about him?
I can tell
that this subordinate
makes Mr. Gao nervous and uneasy.
What about me?
Do I make you nervous?
Charles, you're avoiding me.
Zuo Lin Lin.
Don't be like this.
You agreed to treat Gao Zhun
because you couldn't let go of me, right?
This is inappropriate.
Have we ever cared about what's appropriate?
I know you hate me,
and that's why you can't forget me.
Charles.
- Lin Lin.
- Charles.
Follow the signs and meet us outside.
It's me.
Dr. Fang.
Close your eyes.
Okay.
Now, do as I say.
Come on.
Breathe in.
One.
Two.
Three.
Breathe out.
You did well.
Now, we have to get out of here.
Don't go.
- Don't go.
- I'm here.
Please, Dr. Fang.
- Don't leave me.
- I'm not leaving you.
Please, Dr. Fang.
- Don't...
- I just want to get you out of here.
Don't leave me.
We're out.
Get down.
Gao Zhun.
It's me, Fang Chi.
Listen to me.
We're out now.
We're both in a safe place.
You can open your eyes and see.
Dr. Fang.
I'm here.
Gao Zhun, look at me.
I want you to look at me.
See?
I'm right here.
Dr. Fang.
Please don't leave me.
I...
I really need you.
I know.
I'm here.
I won't leave you.
Can you...
go upstairs by yourself?
I can.
Dr. Fang.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Don't say that.
I willingly did so.
What?
I said,
I'm willing to help you out of the darkness.
I hope that one day,
you'll let me into your nightmares.
I...
I'll try, Dr. Fang.
Fang Chi.
You can call me "Fang Chi".
Fang... Chi.
Fang Chi.
Go on back.
Apologize to Lin Lin for me.
Is it necessary for two grown men
to say goodbye like that?
Do all rich people have some kind of problem?
What's wrong with liking women?
How did you feel after going back yesterday?
Pretty good.
You seem to be in good spirits today.
Let's try desensitization therapy.
Okay.
What should I do?
Relax.
Do as I say.
Close your eyes.
Imagine this.
You're not in the consultation room now.
Then where am I?
In your own bedroom at home.
How does it feel?
It feels...
very safe.
Now, change the location.
An empty place with no one around.
He's afraid of the dark and enclosed spaces.
He doesn't even dare to drive.
He won't even go to underground parking.
You find...
that you're in an underground parking lot.
Tell me.
In your imagination, besides you,
who else is there?
No, I don't want to think about it.
I don't want to think about it.
No.
You're safe.
I'm right here with you.
Tell me.
Who is there?
No one.
There's no one.
- Who is it?
- No!
Gao Zhun.
- Who is it?
- No!
Who is it?
No!
Fang Chi. No.
I didn't know.
Don't be afraid.
It's okay.
It's not your fault.
I know you didn't mean to.
Wait for me here.
Don't do anything foolish, okay?
Look.
I need to go take care of this.
I'll be back in ten minutes.
I... I'll listen to you, Dr. Fang.
I won't do anything.
I won't do a thing.
And...
Remember, it's Fang Chi.
Dr. Fang...
Fang Chi.
- Your hand...
- I told you.
It's fine.
Sit down. Let's continue.
We're still continuing?
Regarding your symptoms,
I'd like to change the treatment plan.
It's just that my method
has always been controversial in the field.
Do you... want to try?
I can try.
I'm just afraid...
Gao Zhun.
Do you trust me?
I trust you.
Many people use self-harm
to escape their subconscious fears.
So, what you did just now was subconscious.
Don't worry about it.
Are you afraid of pain?
Not when you're with me.
What is this?
A pointer.
If I find out that you're lying to me,
you'll be punished by me.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Is there anyone around you
who makes you feel afraid lately?
No.
Yes, there is.
Who?
It's Justin.
What did he do to scare you?
He...
He didn't do anything.
He asked me if I'd seen "Spring Fever."
It's that kind of film between men...
A gay romance.
Yes.
I've seen it.
But I told him I hadn't.
You love Justin.
I don't.
Then what about Zuo Lin Lin?
What about your relationship with her?
I love her.
Answer again.
There's... There's no love left.
I can't give it to her.
I have no desire for her either.
What about someone other than Zuo Lin Lin?
Didn't you say you trust me?
Then why won't you tell me the truth?
I don't have love.
I don't have it for anyone else either.
The truth.
I want to hear the truth.
Who is that person?
Who is it?
Who... Who... Who is it?
You.
It's you.
The truth is...
my love...
is for you.
Cut!
Using this stuff for treatment?
The screenwriter really is daring.
But Director, do those two...
really need to hug for so long?
Mr. Wu, there's emotion between them.
It has to be handled this way.
But you're different.
You need to be violent and intense.
The next scene is all on you.
Understood.
I'll be as shameless as I need to be.
It's okay.
How are you? You okay, Zhun?
I'm fine.
Just let me recover for five minutes.
Sure.
Could you hold this for me?
Zhun, I'll head to
the rental house and wait for you.
Why are you everywhere?
Wait, the rental house?
What scene are you two doing?
An intimate scene.
Are you upset?
The next scene...
you'd better not watch.
Why shouldn't I watch?
It's just a minor subplot of two people
rubbing against each other through pants.
Hey... Can you not be so mean?
Scene 82.
Cameras A and B ready.
Ready. Three, two, one.
Action!
Cut!
Mr. Wu, the feeling isn't right.
You look gentle toward Mr. Zhang,
but you're violent to the core.
During your contact with Mr. Zhang,
your darkness, your violence,
and your sense of destruction...
You need to release it all.
Let's do another take.
Then let's make it... even more intense.
- Okay.
- All departments, get ready.
Three, two, one.
Action!
Fuck!
I'm going to die on top of you.
Zhen Xin.
Cut!
It's a wrap.
Why are you here?
I heard it.
Heard what?
Just now, you called my name.
I told you.
If you can't hold your liquor, drink less.
But you didn't listen.
If I were to wake up now,
it would be very awkward.